#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/aliya-tarmo-06073a1b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Networking Producing Casting

# Aliya Tarmo

### Content Producer

Greater Vancouver Metropolitan Area

## Summary

Senior Producer with an international footprint across Australia and North America. 10+ years of industry experience in captaining Live Action, CG and Augmented Reality projects across various platforms and formats.

Broad experience working hand in hand with clients within health, government, automotive, not-for-profit, and tech sectors. Distilling complex problems and briefs into compelling campaigns.

Experience in leading multidisciplinary teams, nurturing the growth of both individuals and companies.

# Experience

123w (One Twenty Three West)
Senior Producer
December 2021 - Present (3 years 3 months)
Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

### Company Profile

We are an independent idea & design collective founded in 2013 and based in Vancouver & Toronto. Our model is about low overhead and high talent and our 15 working Creative Directors share the CD role equally, ensuring a diverse mix of perspectives, opinions and styles for every project.

Clients worked with include - Destination BC, BC Children's Hospital, Plenty of Fish, Sleeman Breweries, Kal Tire, Hello Fresh, Rocky Mountaineer, Indigenous Tourism BC, Vancouver Fraser Port Authority

Guerilla Creative Senior Producer April 2019 - August 2021 (2 years 5 months) Melbourne, Australia

Company Profile

We are storytellers at heart and we are damn good at spinning a visual yarn.

Creating engaging video and digital content isn't just a job for us...we live for it.

Our imaginative team of cinematography connoisseurs are trusted by some of Australia's largest brands, TV networks, PR and Ad agencies, both locally in Melbourne, but also interstate and even internationally.

Clients worked with include: Monash University, Amazon, Vic Roads, Westpac, Allianz, CSL and St Vincent De Paul

Rotor Studios Key Account Manager May 2018 - April 2019 (1 year) Melbourne, Australia

Company Profile

Rotor Studios is a multi award winning, full service production company specialising in Live-action Content Production, Computer Generated Content (CG) and Software Development.

Key Account - Toyota Motor Corporation Australia

PurpleMonky Producer December 2015 - May 2018 (2 years 6 months) Melbourne, Australia

Company Profile

Our mission is to produce unique films and products for individuals, companies, and audiences through nimble production methods, exceptional customer care, and the talents of creatives, artists, producers and film makers.

We are a film and video production power house focused on the ideation, creation, production, and execution of commercial, corporate, and digital video content.

Our talented film makers produce commercial and corporate videos with a focus on publishing high quality content via websites, apps and social media channels.

Clients worked with include: Toyota, Square, VicHealth, V/Line, CBus, Cancer Council, Sukin, LazyBoy Furniture and Heart Foundation

Trisko Talent Management
Talent Agent
January 2012 - December 2014 (3 years)
Vancouver, Canada Area

Company Profile

Trisko Talent Management Inc. is a Vancouver-based agency that represents actors for film, television, motion capture, commercials, and voice over. We are proud to partner with both established and developing talent in all departments as well as numerous US based agencies and managers. We believe in providing artistic opportunities that challenge and motivate our clients. We encourage artists' exploration of their craft and assist in the development of their full potential. Working with our clients to achieve their dreams is the driving force behind the Trisko Talent team

My roster at Trisko Talent Management spanned across all mediums including film, television and commercials and print

#### **VANOC**

Communications Coordinator (Contract)
December 2009 - March 2010 (4 months)

Company Profile

The Vancouver Organizing Committee for the 2010 Olympic and Paralympic Winter Games was the non-profit organization responsible for planning, organizing, financing and staging the 2010 Winter Olympics and 2010 Winter Paralympics.

My primary responsibility as the Communications Coordinator at the 2010 Olympic Games involved organizing and executing press conferences with both foreign and domestic medal winners at the International Media and Broadcast Centre.

Marriott Hotel
Guest Services/Concierge
February 2008 - July 2009 (1 year 6 months)

### Company Profile

Marriott International, Inc is a global leading lodging company based in Bethesda, Maryland, USA, with more than 4,300 properties in 81 countries and territories. Marriott International reported revenues of nearly \$14 billion in fiscal year 2014. The company operates and franchises hotels and licenses vacation ownership resorts under 19 brands. Marriott has been consistently recognized as a top employer and for its superior business ethics

### Education

Vancouver Film School

Business Diploma, Entertainment Business Management · (2010 - 2012)

Vancouver Community College

Business Diploma, Tourism and Hospitality · (2008 - 2010)